🎶
Day 1073
Still asleep
although stuck in this never ending fever dream
don't know why
It's waiting right before my door
I feel it's craving for me
I'm not void of pain
I can feel every cell as if I'm wide awake
when he does rip me open in my chest
and let me endure the pain
🎶
Day 1074
Still alive
If it wants it can make me feel a hundred knives
at a time
I try to move but all is frozen
in my body fully
It does stay outside
while it waits and I don't know why
So on the verge of insane when I hear it call
I'm not more than an anguished soul
Oh I wonder how I'm still alive with these scars
Only thing I know by now is I'm stuck
Only when I call it out by it's name he snaps
and would end my life with these claws
Try to fall asleep but it wakes me up
Vivid once again, my throat has been cut
Struggling to breathe with blood in my lungs
It won't let me die from things that it does
It's waiting for me
I know it's waiting for me
Though I hope one day this mere becomes a bad memory
Forever playing with me
And it seems to know no bound in how much pain I can be
Don't know why I've been placed and since been stuck in this place
Don't know why I'm still praying for the time I awake
Don't know why god lets anybody suffer this pain
Just one more moment, moment
Maybe there is a glimpse of end in sight
🎶